tunescoop.com 2012-12-30

# TuneScoop - Free music hosting and Sharing

This TuneScoop Privacy Policy, in conjunction with the AUP, Terms of Service and other terms and conditions of use which are incorporated herein by reference and may be posted and applicable to specific services, governs your use of the TuneScoop website and are collectively referred to as the "Agreement".

TuneScoop may modify the Agreement which will become effective immediately upon posting on the website. Your continued use of the website and any associated services, the "Services", indicates your acceptance of the Agreement.

Any Content uploaded by you to TuneScoop becomes published Content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

TuneScoop uses IP addresses to measure usage and analyze trends, administer the website and collect information for its databases.

We will not rent, sell or share your information with third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such actions are necessary to: conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on us; protect and defend the rights or property of TuneScoop, or visitors of TuneScoop; identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties; co-operate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

Third-party websites linked to TuneScoop are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These websites may collect personally identifiable information about you and place a cookie on your browser. TuneScoop is not responsible for the privacy practices of the third-party websites and companies.

TuneScoop is not responsible if you volunteer personal information online that is accessible to the public. You may receive unsolicited messages from other parties or it may be used in a manner that violates the law, your personal privacy or your safety. By submitting such information, you assume the risks and sole liability arising as a result of such information being displayed.

If you are not a resident of the Canada, you understand and agree that TuneScoop stores and processes your information on computers located in the Canada, any by providing any data to TuneScoop, you consent to the transfer of such information to Canada.

In the event that TuneScoop is acquired or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of any change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, TuneScoop may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred or used.

Although we strive to protect your personal information, TuneScoop cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
